Anything?
No one goes in or out.
Figures.
Faraday was right. He changed sites.
It was a lost cause.
Dropped the ball on this one.
Must be big if Arasaka's willing to
clean house over a stolen car.
If only that Faraday'd tell us
what the fuck we after.
This stinks of high-risk shit.
"The biggest fish is always
the one that got away"?
Want me to dig deeper into Tanaka?
Nah, sniffing around
‘Saka business is a fixer's job.
"You are being paid to check off
the boxes on my checklist."
Yeah, yeah.
I went ahead and sicced Kiwi on him.
I guess we'll see what we find.
So we're on hold for now?
We'll need to find a way to kill time…
Said yourself, right?
Alright, fine.
I'm here for Aldo.
Yeah? Who's asking?
Maine sent me.
Hah? You Davis?
Uh…
Huh?
I'm David.
Davis?
David! Not Davis! David!
The fuck you screaming for?!
I can hear you.
David? You're Pilar's carrier pigeon.
Pilar's?
Was you, wasn't it? The punk kid
who klepped and junked the ‘Saka limo?
Yeah… First time on the job.
Could've collected 5K for it at least
if you hadn't gone and trashed it to hell.
-I'll remember that next time.
-Huh?
I'll do better next time!
Next time, eh?
Guess we'll see if last time wasn't
a stroke of beginner's luck.
What do you mean?
Nothing personal.
Won't take long to see if
you're the shit or just a lil' shit stain.
Hear about that cyberpsycho up in Watson?
They just keep popping up.
Yeah, took out two NCPD on patrol.
Saw the scroll. It was damn bloody.
A single launcher hit
turned him into so much canned paste…
Hey David! How've you been?
Uh…
What's up? You need something?
Uh. Got this package here
from Maine for Pilar.
Oh…
Bro!
Bro?
Delivery from Maine!
Fucking finally!
You know how many of
the boys'd kill to get these cyberhands?
Preeem!
Need me to excuse you now, or…?
He have anything else for me to do?
Bro?
Yeah, fuck off. Tip him on his way out.
He's your errand boy!
Fork it over yourself, cheap-ass!
It's bulletproof!
So do I clock out now?
Uh… Looks that way.
Oh. Cool…
Whoa?! All this for a tip?!
You're adorable.
See you later, David.
You came?
You told me to come.
Maine bullied me into it.
Wha… Maine?
Asshole.
You're kidding.
You're telling me. It's my day off.
Sorry to hear it.
No offense, but you're not
exactly built like a punk.
You look like you'd tweak out
after one or two more implants.
I'm not that weak!
Keep up, then.
Ever use one?
No.
Gloria never let you carry?
Well, better start now than never.
Could teach ya if ya want.
Think I'll stick with the Sandevistan.
Hey.
Yes?
So, you're a netrunner?
Yeah. And?
Nothing. Just… do netrunners need to run?
Netrunner, edgerunner. No difference.
Stamina is everything.
Don't leave the house empty-handed
from now on, you hear me?
Every day. You check for your wallet,
your condom, and your gun.
Sure, some punks go straight chrome.
But it's gonna be a while before you can
stay alive with just your cyberware.
Until then, that gun's gonna be
your backup plan.
Hey.
Yes?
How old are you anyway?
How're things with Lucy?
Huh?
You treating her right?
No, I didn't mean… Well, your age
and skills don't really add up.
Skill has nothing to do with age.
It's all about hard work.
Besides, only idiots talk down to
people younger than them.
Like who?
Like long-armed techies.
What do you mean "treating her right"?
Wait… You still haven't done it?
What are we talking about exactly?
David, you're gonna need to
grow a pair of cajones
and I ain't just talking
in a cyberpunk sense.
Thought I saw you two
talking the other day.
At the party after the limo heist.
He likes to act like
my mentor or something.
He got grabby, so I fried him a bit
and told him to scram.
Huh.
How about you?
You serious about edgerunning?
I'm not into her like that.
C'mon kid, we've all got eyes.
She's not into me like that.
Yeah, probably.
Why are you asking?
You just don't seem the type.
Why?!
Tell me!
I just don't know how much of it was real.
What you mean?
Said she wants to go to the moon.
The moon?
Yeah, it's her dream or whatever.
You're faster than you look.
Yeah, yeah.
Really. Doubted you could keep up.
Sarcasm? I'm not that easy to get rid of.
Never said nothing about that to me.
So she lied?
Who knows? Just ask her.
She was probably just stalling me, but…
But we went to the moon together.
With her special BD.
You had a date on the moon?
Shit, you don't get much more
romantic than that in Night City.
Here, a training regimen.
This is just the bare minimum.
You're on your own after today.
If you're serious about this,
you'll need to keep up. And then…
And then?
How long has she been with you guys?
Been about a year? Kiwi brought her in.
Said she found a natural.
What about before that?
I don't know.
Like I said, ask her yourself.
I don't give two shits
about people's pasts
so long as they can pull their weight.
Thought you'd say that.
'Ey, keep it down!
Damn!
Jeez, that's loud.
Gross.
Seriously.
What's your problem, eh?
Why you pissing in the street?!
'Ey, homie! You hear me?!
Leave him alone.
Bye bro.
You aiming for hole-in-one?
I'm talking to ya! Ya hear me?!
Listen, we don't like
walking in piss, asshole.
Alright? This sidewalk belongs to us…
Oh, shit! That's one hell of an implant!
Gives whole new meaning to
the phrase "hard as ir--"
Hey…
Da…
vid…
move…
Not the time to freeze, kid!
Fucking capped him!
-Got bits of Pilar on me…
-Gimme that!
Fucker!
You had no fucking right!
Fucking psycho trash!
Stupid, you'll flatline
faster than you can land a shot!
Let me go!
Die!
Shit, of all times…
Kiwi! Reset Becca's system!
On it.
Where's Lucy?!
Hey, asshole!
David!
Lucy!
I'm alright.
Good.
You're bleeding…
I'm the only one
who was allowed to kill him…
Don't touch me.
Do you need medical?
No.
Dorio, take Lucy to see a ripperdoc.
I'll stay with Kiwi until the pigs arrive.
Someone's gotta explain this mess.
You heard him.
You go with 'em, kid.
Huh?
We'll tell 'em we took him
out after he zeroed Pilar.
They'll file it as a cyberpsycho incident,
but it's better that you ain't here.
But…
I saw what you did.
Time you stopped thinking like a rookie.
You lot again? I'm not actually
a licensed physicist, you know.
I didn't volunteer to come either.
Charming.
I'll go alone.
Clean her up and get her home.
-You're leaving?
-Maine said you could take his car.
Lucy.
-Here's fine.
-Sure.
Good night.
Um… Can we talk?
This way.
Aw. It's all cloudy.
That moon BD you showed me
was pretty sweet.
I had something
I wanted to talk about, too.
Oh?
I know how it must look but…
What I told you that day before?
I wasn't lying.
It was the first time I told anyone.
That's…
That's good.
I didn't want to think you were lying.
What if I'm lying now?
-I don't think you are.
-Why not?
-'Cause I don't like that.
-That's crazy.
You should've said something earlier.
I couldn't.
Why not?
You were so mad at me.
I wasn't mad.
Was too.
I wasn't mad, just…
Well, yeah. Guess I was.
See?
I was angry, but…
I wasn't pissed at you.
Wouldn't have saved you if I did.
-Liar.
-I'm not.
No, that's a lie.
You're the kind of guy who'll jump in fire
to save someone, even if you get burned.
You're that type.
Is that why you think I won't make it?
Maine thinks I will. Why can't…
No, it's not that. You'd make
a good edgerunner, I think.
I really do.
So what's the problem?
You don't make a name
as a cyberpunk by how you live.
You're remembered by how you die.
It's not the life or the end you deserve.
What makes me any different from you?
I have nowhere else to go.
I don't either.
You and I are worlds apart.
How?!
I'll take you to the moon!
I promise!
I just don't want you to die.
I won't.